imaginelearning.com 2019-03-02

# Imagine Learning

Imagine Learning
Site Privacy Policy
Last modified: 16 May 2017
Imagine Learning, Inc. (“Imagine Learning,” “we” or “us”) respects your privacy and is
committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy. This Site
Privacy Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you when you visit
our websites located at www.imaginelearning.com and university.imaginelearning.com
(collectively, the “Site”), how we use such information, with whom we share it, how we
protect it, and the choices we offer you regarding our collection and use of such
information. This Site Privacy Policy does not govern Imagine Learning’s student-focused
products and services, specifically Imagine Language & Literacy, Imagine Español,
Imagine Math, and Imagine Math Facts and their associated websites including:
go.imaginelearning.com, my.imaginelearning.com, client.imaginelearning.com,
espanol.imaginelearning.com, bigbrainz.com/web, and lms.thinkthroughmath.com. Please
visit https://imaginelearning.com/privacy for the Privacy Policy governing these student-
focused products and services.
Please read this Site Privacy Policy carefully. By using the Site, you agree to the terms of
this Site Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Site Privacy Policy, do
not use the Site.
Contents
    1.  Types of Information We Collect
    2.  How We Use the Information We Collect
    3.  Information We Share
    4.  Your Choices
    5.  Accessing and Correcting Your Personal Information
    6.  Imagine Learning Protects Your Information
    7.  Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
    8.  Links to Other Sites
    9.  Changes to Our Site Privacy Policy
    10. Questions and Suggestions
Types of Information We Collect
We may collect personal information from you, meaning information about you that can
uniquely identify you, such as your name, mailing address, email address, and telephone
number, if you choose to provide us with such information. We may also collect
information about you that does not uniquely identify you, such as information about
your school or organization, or related to your account settings and preferences, if you
Copyright © Imagine Learning, Inc.

choose to provide us with such information. We collect such information in various ways,
including if you:
    •   register for an Imagine University account on the Site;
    •   place an order for products, materials or services on the Site; and/or
    •   request information from us by submitting a form on the Site.
    •   In addition, when you visit Site, we may collect certain information by automated
        means, such as cookies. A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor’s
        computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s
        browser or to store information or settings in the browser. We also may use third-
        party website analytics tools (such as Google Analytics) that collect information
        about visitor traffic on our Site. The information we may collect by automated
        means may include, but is not limited to, the following:
    •   information about the devices you use to access the Internet (such as the IP
        address and the type of the device, its operating system type and web browser);
    •   dates, times and duration of visits to the Site (including whether you are a repeat
        or first time visitor); and/or
    •   information on actions taken on the Site (such as page views and site navigation
        patterns).
Your web browser may let you choose your preference as to whether you want to allow
websites to collect personal information over time about your online activities across
different websites or online services. As stated above, we may enable third parties to
collect information in connection with the Site. This Site Privacy Policy does not apply to,
and we are not responsible for, any collection of information by third parties on our Site.
How We Use the Information We Collect
Email Address: This is used as your Imagine University login; it uniquely identifies your
Imagine University account. Correspondence concerning your Imagine University
account will be sent to this email address.
Imagine University Information: Some information used in Imagine University, such as
district and school name, are required for reporting purposes. Other information, such as
course feedback and user preferences, may also be collected.
We may use the information we obtain about you to:
    •   understand your needs and interests and tailor the Site and our products and
        services accordingly;
    •   maintain a record of your transactions on the Site;
    •   respond to your questions and comments and provide customer support;
    •   communicate with you about our products and services and our offers, events,
        and promotions;
    •   operate, evaluate, and improve our business and the products and services we
        offer;
    •   enforce our End-User Software License Agreement and other agreements, as
        applicable; and/or
    •   comply with applicable legal requirements and industry standards.
Copyright © Imagine Learning, Inc.

    •   We also may use the information we obtain about you in other ways for which we
        provide specific notice at the time of collection.
Information We Share
We may disclose aggregated information about our users without restriction. However,
we do not share your personal information with third parties except as described in this
Site Privacy Policy.
We may disclose your personal information to our subsidiaries and affiliates, or to
contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business.
Such third parties are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information
confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. We may
also disclose your personal information to: (i) comply with any court order, law or legal
process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request; (ii) enforce or
apply our End-User Software License Agreement and other agreements, as applicable;
and/or (iii) if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights,
property, or safety of Imagine Learning, our customers, or others. We also reserve the
right to disclose your personal information to a buyer or other transferee in the event of
a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, sale or other transfer of
some or all of our assets.
Your Choices
We offer you the following choices about what information we collect from you and how
we communicate with you:
Cookies: Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be
notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note,
however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the
Site’s features.
Website Analytics: You may opt-out of the collection and use of data about you by
Google Analytics on the Site by visiting https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout and
downloading and installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.
Marketing Emails: You may choose not to receive marketing email communications from
us by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of our marketing emails.
Newsletter: You may choose to unsubscribe from our newsletter by adjusting your
preferences using your account on the Site. Please note that unsubscribing from our
newsletter will not unsubscribe you from our marketing emails. You may unsubscribe
from our marketing emails as set forth above.
Accessing and Correcting Your Personal Information
You can review and change your personal information by logging into your Imagine
University account on the Site and visiting your account profile page. You may also send
us an email at imagineuniversity@imaginelearning.com to request access to, correct, or
delete any personal information that you have provided to us.
Copyright © Imagine Learning, Inc.

Imagine Learning Protects Your Information
Imagine Learning uses SSL and https (a standardized method of securely transferring
information between your computer and Imagine Learning) to protect personal
information under our control from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration. In addition,
Imagine Learning stores your information behind firewalls on separate secure servers.
Please note that no electronic transmission of information can be entirely secure. We
cannot guarantee that the security measures we have in place will never be defeated or
fail, or that such measures will always be sufficient or effective.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) is designed to protect
children's privacy while using the Internet. The Site is not directed to, and Imagine
Learning does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from, children under
the age of 13. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child
under the age of 13, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any
information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us at
privacy@imaginelearning.com. For more information about COPPA, please visit
http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html.
Links to Other Sites
This Site may contain links to other websites operated by third parties. Such links are
provided for your convenience only, and if you access any other websites linked to this
Site you do so at your own risk. We are not responsible for the content of any such
websites, for the security of information you provide on such websites, or the products
and services sold on them, nor are we responsible or liable for any loss or damage that
may arise from your use of such websites. Links to other websites do not imply Imagine
Learning’s endorsement of any content, advertising, products, services, or other materials
on or available from such websites. Imagine Learning strongly suggests you read the
terms of use and privacy policy that govern each website you visit.
Changes to Our Site Privacy Policy
Imagine Learning reserves the right to update or change this Site Privacy Policy at any
time. If we make a material change to our Site Privacy Policy, we will indicate on the Site
that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new policy. When we
make a material change to how we use your personal information, we will provide you
with an opportunity to opt out of such new or different use. The date this Site Privacy
Policy was last revised is at the top of this page. You are responsible for periodically
reviewing the Site and this Site Privacy Policy to check for any updates or changes.
Questions and Suggestions
If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please write to us at:
Copyright © Imagine Learning, Inc.

    Imagine Learning, Inc.
    Attn: Privacy Inquiry
    382 W Park Circle
    Provo, Utah 84604
    Tel.: 801.377.5071
    Email: privacy@imaginelearning.com
Copyright © Imagine Learning, Inc.
